https://www.vipstructures.com/privacy/

BIM
Drone (UAS)
BIM
Drone (UAS)
Last Modified: June 3, 2015
VIP Structures (“VIP Structures,” “Company,” “our,” “we,” or “us”) respects your privacy.
This Policy applies to and describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit, use, and interact with our website currently located at https://www.vipstructures.com/ (the “Website”).
Please read this Policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we collect it and will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is to not access, use, or interact with our Website. By accessing, using, and/or interacting with our Website, you agree to this Privacy Policy. This Policy may change from time to time. Your continued access and/or use of our Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the Policy periodically for updates.
Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It
We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information:
We collect directly from you when you provide it to us:
by which you may be personally identified such as your name, company name, address, email address, postal address, telephone number, cell phone number, date of birth or age, credit card or debit card number, or any other identifier by which you may be contacted online or offline (“personal information”).
We collect automatically as you navigate through and use the Website:
that is about you but individually does not identify you, such as statistical data related to your use of the Website;
about your use of and interaction with the Website; and/or
about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website and usage details, and location of such equipment.
Information You Provide to Us
We may ask you to or you may otherwise provide some personal information if you do any of the following on or through the Website:
contact us from the Website by, for example, filling in forms on our Website;
request information;
share a message or comment with us (via email, text, or other electronic messages) or through others who use the Website (on or through the Website), or otherwise providing information on or through the Website;
perform searches on the Website;
carry out any other transaction on or through the Website; or
request further services, or alert us of any issues or problems with our Website, services, products, materials, events etc.
You may choose whether to enter personal information when you visit our Website. You are not required to do so. If you choose not to provide the information that we request and/or otherwise may be required to do so under certain circumstances listed above, we may be unable to respond to your request, provide a requested service, or proceed with a requested transaction etc. We do, however, collect, store, and/or use personal information when it is voluntarily submitted to us, as noted above.
Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies
As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, and/or browsing actions and patterns, including:
details of your visits to, use of, and interaction with our Website, including traffic data, location data, and other meta data including information regarding resources that you access and use on the Website; and
information about your computer or mobile device and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system and browser type, location based data including geographic location of your computer or mobile device, and unique computer or mobile device identifiers.
The information we collect automatically is statistical data and may include personal information, or we may maintain the statistical data or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:
estimate our audience size and usage patterns;
store information about your preferences and particular uses of our Website, allowing us to customize and/or improve the performance, content and functionality of our Website according to your individual interests; and
recognize you when you return to our Website.
The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:
Cookies (or browser cookies). A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access or properly use certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website; or
Google Analytics. This is a specific type of metric tracking. See Google’s privacy policy http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ for further details regarding the type of information collected using this tool.
VIP Structures does not use tracking or measurement tools that would allow your individual browsing activity to be tracked across third-party websites or that would give information about you as an individual to third-parties based on your browsing activity.
How We Use Your Information
We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:
to present our Website and their contents to you;
for search engine optimization purposes;
to customize and/or improve the performance, content and functionality of our Website;
to provide you with information, technical support, registrations, products or services that you request from us;
to allow third party service providers to perform services on our behalf;
to fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it;
to carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection;
to notify you about changes to our Website, or any products or services we offer or provide though any of the foregoing;
to prevent and detect fraud and other misuse of the Website;
in any other way we may describe when you provide the information; and
for any other purpose with your consent.
We may also use your information to contact you about our own or third-parties’ goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, please see the “Opt-Out” Section below.
Disclosure of Your Information
We may disclose aggregated information about our Website’s users, and information that does not identify any individual, to third parties without restriction.
We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this Policy:
to contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them;
to a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, acquisition, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by us about our Website’s users is among the assets transferred;
to fulfill the purpose for which you provide it;
for any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information; and/or
with your consent.
We may also disclose your personal information:
to comply with any court order or subpoena, law or legal process, including responding to any government, regulatory request, law enforcement agency or other public agency;
to enforce or apply our Website’s terms of use and other agreements; and/or
if we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of VIP Structures, our customers or others, or if we feel that such disclosure may prevent the instigation of a crime, protect the security or integrity of our Website, or enable us to take precautions against liability.
Accessing and Correcting Your Information
You may also send us an e-mail at privacy@nullvipstructures.com to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. To the extent applicable, we cannot attempt to fully delete your personal information. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.
Links to Other Sites
The Website may also include links to other websites. Once you leave the Website for any reason per any means, VIP Structure’s Privacy Policy no longer applies and VIP Structure is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those sites. It is incumbent upon you to be familiar with the privacy policies of other websites you may visit.
Social Media, Widgets and Open Forums
Our Website may allow you to engage with social media services, such as Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest, LinkedIn, YouTube and Google+ (“Social Networks”), and widgets such as the “Share this” button, or interactive mini-programs that run on our Website or which link from Social Networks to our Website (“Social Functions”). These Social Functions may access, collect and integrate with your Social Network accounts and information. For example, these Social Functions may collect your IP address, identify which page you are visiting on our Website, or set a cookie. For example, if you use certain Social Functions, you may be asked to enter your Social Network credentials. If you choose to use these Social Functions, you may be sharing certain Social Network profile elements with us, including your name, date of birth/age, comments, contacts, email address, photos or favorite teams. This sharing is subject to each Social Network’s own privacy policy and terms of use. We do not control those Social Networks or your profiles on those services. We do not modify your privacy settings on those services or establish rules about how your personal information on those services will be used.  Social Functions are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Website. Your interactions with them are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing them. Please refer to the privacy settings in your Social Network account to manage the data that is shared with us through your account.
Further, information you include and transmit online in a publicly accessible blog, chat room or Social Network, or that you share in an open forum such as an in-person panel or survey, may be viewed and used by others without any restrictions. As noted above, we do not control such uses of your personal information, and by using such services you assume the risk and acknowledge that the personal information provided by you may be viewed and used by us and/or third parties for any number of purposes and that the usage restrictions set forth in this Privacy Policy do not apply to such services.
Opt-Out
To opt-out of having your information stored or shared with other parties, or receiving communications from us, please contact us in writing at VIP Structures, One Websters Landing, Syracuse NY, 13202, send an email to privacy@nullvipstructures.com , or indicate so on online forms as may be applicable.
Children Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)
Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age, and we do not specifically target the Website to children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any information to, on or through the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information to, on or through the Website, or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, email address or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us in writing at VIP Structures, One Websters Landing, Syracuse NY, 13202, or send an email to privacy@nullvipstructures.com.
Your California Privacy Rights
California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us in writing at VIP Structures, One Websters Landing, Syracuse NY, 13202, or send an email to privacy@nullvipstructures.com.
Security and Disclaimer
We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information under our control from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls.
Unfortunately, no computer system nor the transmission of information via the internet is completely secure. Although we have implemented commercially reasonable safeguards to protect your personal information that we collect and store, no data security safeguards are foolproof and we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.
Policy Changes
VIP Structures reserves the right to make changes to its Privacy Policy at any time. A new policy, when posted, will apply to everyone using our Website and will replace any and all prior policies. The date of the last revision to the Privacy Policy is identified at the top of the page. You should check periodically for changes to our Privacy Policy.
Contact Information
Your privacy is very important to us. If you have any questions or comments about this Policy and our privacy practices, please contact us at:
